

Hi, I'm Alex - I'm a **product designer** with a background in **front-end development**. I'm particularly interested in **user experience, usability and research** and its applications to improve people's lives. My native language is **Spanish** and I'm fluent in **English**.

# **Experience**

## Product designer — Entrepreneur

#### **EventNest**

Oct 2024 — Present Spain — Remote

I am working on the creation of a **marketplace** that helps event organizers and promoters find the services they need to develop their activities. The project is currently in its initial phase, where I am conducting the necessary research to define the **MVP** (Minimum Viable Product) to begin working on.

## Product designer — Entrepreneur

#### Geomites

Mar 2023 — Present Spain — Remote

I lead the UX and UI design of this project, where we are designing and developing a **mobile video** game for iOS and Android platforms in an agile environment.

## **Product designer** — Freelance

Apr 2022 — Present Spain — Remote

I work as a product designer for different companies and sectors. My main freelance activities include designing and developing **company websites**, designing **corporate documents**, and participating in the **design process** of various products or services.

## Marketing manager — Contract

#### Promam

Jul 2017 — Sep 2021 Spain — Onsite

I was responsible for marketing and design tasks, managing the design and development of the **company's website** and led **SEO** positioning campaigns. I spearheaded marketing campaigns on social media and organized and developed the design of various products necessary for the company's operations, including **catalogs, advertisements, and documents**. I also collaborated with stakeholders to organize the **marketing and sales strategy**.

## **Education**

# Google & Coursera, Interaction Design Foundation

2021 - Present

Design thinking: The ultimate guide, User Experience: Begginer's Guide, Foundations of User Experience, User research, Gestalt psychology, Human-Computer interaction, Design for the 21st century, Emotional design, Information visualization, Mobile user experience, Visual design, UI design patterns

## **Rey Juan Carlos University**

Marketing degree

2011 - 2016

## **Skills**

UX research, UX design, UI design, Wireframing, Prototyping, Problem solving, Communication, Design systems, Usability

### **Tools**

Sketch, Figma, Adobe Creative suite, Framer, Webflow, Wordpress, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Axure, Asana, Jira, ChatGPT, Midjourney, NotebookLM

#### Contact

alejandromorenomartin.com +34 618110583 alejandromorenomartin1990@gmail.com